Yesterday Aunt Daisy was at the supermarket.
Hôm qua Dì Daisy ở siêu thị.
Then she was at the bookshop.
Rồi dì ở hiệu sách.
Then she was at the train station.
Rồi dì ở ga tàu.
Then she was at the hospital.
Rồi dì ở bệnh viện.
Then she was at the bank.
Rồi dì ở ngân hàng.
And then she was at the park next to the bank.
Và rồi dì ở công viên cạnh ngân hàng.
Which park was Aunt Daisy at?
Dì Daisy ở công viên nào?
Two.
Hai.
Yesterday Ella and Flo were with our grandparents.
Hôm qua Ella và Flo đi với ông bà.
First they were at the bus stop.
Đầu tiên họ ở trạm xe buýt.
Then they were at the zoo.
Rồi họ ở sở thú.
After that they were at the library.
Sau đó họ ở thư viện.
Next they were at the swimming pool.
Tiếp theo họ ở bể bơi.
Then they were at the shopping centre.
Rồi họ ở trung tâm mua sắm.
And after that they were at the park next to the shopping centre.
Và sau đó họ ở công viên cạnh trung tâm mua sắm.
Which park were Ella and Flo at?
Ella và Flo ở công viên nào?
Three.
Ba.
Yesterday I was very busy.
Hôm qua mình rất bận.
In the morning I was at the supermarket.
Buổi sáng mình ở siêu thị.
Then I was at the bookshop.
Rồi mình ở hiệu sách.
In the afternoon I was at the cafe with my cousins.
Buổi chiều mình ở quán cà phê với các anh chị em họ.
Then I was at the library looking for a book.
Rồi mình ở thư viện tìm sách.
After that I was at the zoo with my friends.
Sau đó mình ở sở thú với bạn bè.
Next to the zoo there's a park.
Cạnh sở thú có một công viên.
And after the zoo we were in that park.
Và sau khi đi sở thú chúng mình ở công viên đó.
Which park was I at?
Mình ở công viên nào?